Guide to the Olga Rudge Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1916-89; Series IV; 8; (16 boxes)
  - Writings of Others
    - Rainer, Dachine
      - "From America, longago...and now, on leaving England..."" typescript photocopy, 1984
      - Giornale di Venezia: typescript photocopies, inscribed to Olga Rudge by Thérèse Wahlfahrt for Rainer, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2905)
      - "Miss Olga Rudge for her birthday..." typescript autographed and typescript photocopy, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 2906)
      - "Villonaud: For the Deluge": typescript photocopy, n.d.
      - Rise and Fall: 17 Poems: photocopy autographed, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 2907)
      - "songs of past love": photocopy of words and music of Francis Routh settings, autographed (Box 118, Folder 2908)
    - Russell, Peter
      - "Convivio": typescript, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 2909)
      - "Inscription": typescript photocopy, 1972
      - [Newsletter]: mimeograph, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 2910)
      - "Preliminary Notes on the Political and Economic Ideas of Ezra Pound": typescript carbon, corrected, 1948 Sep 16 (Box 118, Folder 2911)
      - [Private Issue Poems] (Box 118, Folder 2912)
      - "Lullamatic": printed, signed, 1972 Jan 29
      - "Smoke, A Vision": printed, signed, 1972 Jan 29
      - "Quintilii Apocalypseos Fragmenta": photocopy, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2913)
      - "Six Sonnets": mimeograph, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2914)
      - "Vingt-cing ans après: An Editor's Personal Statement": typescript carbon photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2915)
    - Singh, G.
      - Articles: offprints and photocopies, some signed, 1975-82, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2916)
      - "New Verse": offprint, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 2917)
      - [Poems] (Box 118, Folder 2918)
      - "And not her mind only...": typescript corrected
      - "The Circle": manuscript, 1987 Oct 14
      - "Pound and Olga"; "Pound and Kabir": typescript signed
      - "Rain on the Olives": typescript, n.d.
      - "To Olga (For her 92nd Birthday)": typescript, corrected, [1987]
      - "To Olga (For Patrizia)": manuscript, 1988 Aug 31
      - "To Pound": manuscript, 1989 May 29
      - "Le riviste letterarie inglesi del novecento": photocopy signed, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 2919)
      - "T. S. Eliot and Bertrand Russell": offprint autographed, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 2920)
    - Swabey, Henry
      - Four Pages. No. 10: mimeograph autographed, 1950 (Box 118, Folder 2921)
    - Terenzio, Jacopo
      - "Maledetti e basta": typescript mimeograph, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 2922)
    - Widershien, Marc
      - The Life of All Worlds, chapter 24: typescript photocopy, with note by Widershien, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 2923)
    - Williams, William Carlos
      - "The Gift: A Poem: Printed at Christmas, 1957 for the friends of William Carlos Williams and Ann and J. Laughlin": printed (Box 118, Folder 2924)
      - "Sketch for a Criticism: The XXX Cantos of Ezra Pound": typescript corrected, signed, 1931 Feb 22 (Box 118, Folder 2925)
    - Wilson, Steuart
      - "The Piano of San Gimignano": manuscript, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2926)
    - Unidentifed authors, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2927-29)
  - Unidentifed and miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 2930-32)
- Financial papers, 1926-89; Series V; 3.75; (8 boxes)
  Series V, Financial Papers, is housed in Boxes 119-26 and has been arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - "Akkounz:" account book, 1934-39 (Box 119, Folder 2933)
  - Account of expenses for Ezra Pound, 1962 Apr-Sep
  - Bank accounts
    Bank statements and receipts
    Checks and checkbooks
    - Banca d'America e d'Italia, 1947-84 (Box 119, Folder 2934-52)
    - Banca d'America e d'Italia, 1985-89, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2953-56)
    - See also: Oversize, Box 158, Box 157, folder 3705
    - Banca Italo-Britannica, 1929 (Box 120, Folder 2957)
    - Cassa di Risparmio di Venezia, 1939-85 (Box 120, Folder 2958-61)
    - Citibank, 1969-88 (Box 120, Folder 2962-74)
    - Dollar Savings and Trust, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 2975)
    - Monte dei Paschi de Siena, 1948-52 (Box 121, Folder 2976)
    - Miscellaneous bank receipts, 1949-87, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2977)
    - Cancelled checks, 1935-87 (Box 121, Folder 2978)
    - Checkbook stubs, 1953-87 (Box 121, Folder 2979-83)
    - Checkbooks, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2984-85)
  - Bills and receipts
    - Accademia Musicale Chigiana, 1936-52 (Box 121, Folder 2986)
    - Books and subscriptions (Box 121, Folder 2987)
    - Funeral expenses for Ezra Pound, [1972] (Box 121, Folder 2988)
    - Groceries, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2989-91)
    - Hotels, 1926-87, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2992-97)
    - Maintenance for 252 Dorsoduro, 1928-87, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2998-3002)
    - Medical, 1942-70, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 3003)
    - Monument for Ezra Pound, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 3004)
    - Postal and telegraph receipts, ca. 1950-87 (Box 122, Folder 3005-09)
    - Reader's Digest, 1982-83 (Box 123, Folder 3010-11)
    - Restaurants
      - Antica Locanda Montin (Box 123, Folder 3012)
      - Da Cici, 1964-69, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3013)
      - La Pergola, 1970-71, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3014)
      - Ristorante Terazza del Doge (Gritti Palace), 1983-89 (Box 123, Folder 3015)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3016)
    - Transportation
      - Airlines, 1955-86, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3017-20)
      - Automobiles, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3021)
      - Railroads, 1951-86, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3022-23)
      - Ships, 1952, 1955 (Box 123, Folder 3024)
    - Utilities
      - 60 San Ambrogio (Rapallo)
        - Electricity, 1945-83 (Box 123, Folder 3025-27)
        - Gas, 1969-85 (Box 123, Folder 3028-29)
        - Telephone, 1969-82 (Box 123, Folder 3030)
        - Water, 1960-69 (Box 123, Folder 3031)
      - 252 Dorsoduro (Venice)
        - Electricity, 1959-90 (Box 124, Folder 3032-34)
        - Gas, 1951-87 (Box 124, Folder 3035-37)
        - Telephone, 1953-89 (Box 124, Folder 3038-41)
        - Television, 1968-88, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 3042-43)
        - Water, 1940-73 (Box 124, Folder 3044-45)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1960-88, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 3046-49)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1960-88, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 3050-53)
  - Claim for war reparations, 1945-58, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 3054)
  - Estate of Louise Birt Baynes, 1957-59 (Box 125, Folder 3055)
  - Insurance policies, 1929-65, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 3056)
  - Leases
    - 2 rue Chamfort (Paris), 1928 (Box 125, Folder 3057)
    - 60 San Ambrogio (Rapallo), 1960-80 (Box 125, Folder 3058)
    - 252 Dorsoduro (Venice), 1935-54 (Box 125, Folder 3059)
  - Royalties
    - New Directions, 1951-71 (Box 125, Folder 3060)
    - Ezra Pound Literary Property Trust, 1972-89 (Box 125, Folder 3061-65)
  - Taxes
    - Esattoria Communale di Siena, 1946-59 (Box 125, Folder 3066)
    - Esattoria Communale di Venezia, 1933-88 (Box 125, Folder 3067-69)
    - Esattoria Consorziale di Rapallo, 1943-88 (Box 125, Folder 3070-71)
    - United States Internal Revenue Service, 1952-89 (Box 126, Folder 3072)
  - Youngstown parking lot, 1952-74 (Box 126, Folder 3073-79)
- Printed Material, 1930-89; Series VI; 3.75; (8 boxes)
  Boxes 127-34 hold Series VI, Printed Material. These have been arranged alphabetically by subject and type of material.
  - Advertisements, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 3080-83)
  - Art catalogues, 1956-88 (Box 127, Folder 3084)
  - Art exhibitions and galleries, 1958-89 (Box 127, Folder 3085-90)
  - Art exhibitions and galleries, 1958-89, n.d. (Box 128, Folder 3091-3101)
  - Arts & Letters: a Center for Classical Studies, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 3102)
  - Associazione Amici della Fenice, 1980-83, n.d. (Box 128, Folder 3103)
  - Associazione Italo-Francese di Cultura, 1978-85, n.d. (Box 128, Folder 3104-05)
  - Bernheimer, Ilse, 1965, 1985 (Box 129, Folder 3106)
  - Book catalogs
    - Dealers', 1962, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 3107)
    - Publishers', 1947-89, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 3108-13)
  - Book jackets and blurbs, 1945-65, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 3114-15)
  - Calendars, 1974-86 (Box 129, Folder 3116-17)
    See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3706
  - Circolo Italo-Britannico Venezia, 1970-78, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 3118)
  - City maps, 1955-71, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 3119)
  - Conferences and congresses, 1970-88, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 3120-21)
  - Dance, 1950-86 (Box 130, Folder 3122)
  - Festival of Two Worlds, 1964-80 (Box 130, Folder 3123-24)
  - Film, 1968-80, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 3125-26)
  - Flower catalogs, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 3127)
  - Fondazione Giorgio Cini, 1972-85 (Box 130, Folder 3128-33)
  - Guarantees and warranties, 1978-84, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 3134)
  - Hotel brochures, n.d. (Box 130, Folder 3135-37)
  - Hotel Gritti Palace Lecture Series, 1981-87 (Box 131, Folder 3138)
  - International Fund for Monuments, 1976-82 (Box 131, Folder 3139-40)
  - Istituto Veneto di Science Lettere ed Arti, 1972-84 (Box 131, Folder 3141-42)
  - Lecture notices, 1960-85, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 3143-45)
  - Medical and psychiatric information, 1931-72, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 3146-47)
  - Museum brochures, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 3148)
  - Periodical information, [1946]-87, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 3149)
  - Periodicals
    - Adam International Review, 1952 (Box 131, Folder 3150)
    - La Destra, 1972 Nov-Dec (Box 131, Folder 3151)
    - Elementi, 1983 Jan-Feb (Box 131, Folder 3152)
    - L'Indice, 1930-31
      See: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3707
    - The Library Chronicle of the University of Texas at Austin, 1970 Nov (Box 131, Folder 3153)
    - The New Yorker, 1960 Sep 3 (Box 132, Folder 3154)
    - La Quinzaine Littéraire, 1966 Nov 1-15
    - Rapallo, 1965 Mar-Apr (Box 132, Folder 3155)
    - Time (Mediterranean Pony Edition), 1945 May 12 (Box 132, Folder 3156)
    - Il Vilaggio, 1978 Jul (Box 132, Folder 3157)
  - Pound, Ezra
    - Conferences, 1953-85, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 3158-60)
    - Exhibitions, 1980-85, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 3161-62)
    - Funeral announcements, 1972 Nov (Box 132, Folder 3163)
    - Performances, 1971-85, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 3164)
    - Publication announcements, 1961-71, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 3165)
    - Miscellaneous articles (photocopies), 1949-86, n.d. (Box 132, Folder 3166-70)
    - Miscellaneous articles (photocopies), 1949-86, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3171-72)
      See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3708
  - Propaganda leaflets of the Salò regime, 1943 Nov (Box 133, Folder 3173)
  - Religious material
    - Holy cards, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3174-75)
    - Parrocchia di Santa Maria del Rosario, 1980-88, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3176)
    - Miscellaneous leaflets and newsletters, 1937-88, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3177-78)
  - Restaurant cards and menus, 1975-86, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3179)
  - Schedules, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3180)
  - Theater programs, 1950-89, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3181-84)
  - Travel brochures, 1934-89, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 3185-88)
    See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3709
  - Unidentified and miscellaneous (Box 134, Folder 3189-92)
    See also: Oversize, Box 157, folder 3710
- Newspaper Clippings, 1923-88; Series VII; 3.5; (7 boxes)
  Series VII, Newspaper Clippings, has been organized aphabetically by subject and is located in Boxes 135-141.
  - Art and Architecture, 1961-87, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3193-96)
  - Astrology, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3197)
  - Biographical sketches, 1950-86, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3198-99)
  - "Cultural Events", 1954-87, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3200-04)
  - Fascism/World War II (Box 135, Folder 3205-07)
    See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3711
  - Festival of Two Worlds (Spoleto), 1965-84, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3208)
  - Film, 1975, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3209)
  - Health and medicine, 1970-87, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 3210)
  - Human interest, 1948-87, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3211-13)
    See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3712
  - Italy, 1964-86, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3214-18)
  - "Jewish question", 1951-82, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3219-20)
  - Literature
    - Beckett, Samuel, 1965-84, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3221)
    - Book reviews, 1960-86, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3222-27)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis, 1982-86 (Box 136, Folder 3228)
    - Bunting, Basil, 1971-85
    - Céline, Louis Ferdinand, 1961-85 (Box 136, Folder 3229)
    - Cocteau, Jean, 1963, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 3230)
    - Connolly, Cyril: articles by, 1964-72, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3231-33)
    - Eliot, T. S., 1950-83, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 3234-37)
    - Frost, Robert, 1963, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3238)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1967, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3239)
    - Giono, Jean, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3240)
    - Golding, William, 1983, n.d.
    - Hemingway, Ernest, 1961-85, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3241-43)
    - Joyce, James, 1964-83, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3244)
    - Kawabata, Yasunari, 1977 Aug 15 (Box 137, Folder 3245)
    - Koestler, Arthur, 1973-84, n.d.
    - Laughlin, James, 1981-84 (Box 137, Folder 3246)
    - Lewis, Wyndham, 1977, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3247)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1971, n.d.
    - Mailer, Norman, 1984, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3248)
    - Malraux, André, 1967, n.d.
    - Montale, Eugenio, 1961-84 (Box 137, Folder 3249)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1965-72, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3250-51)
    - Moravia, Alberto, 1965-84, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3252)
    - Popper, Karl, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 3253)
    - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander, 1975-78 (Box 137, Folder 3254)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1972, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 3255)
    - Yeats, William Butler, 1967-77, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3256)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1962-86, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 3257-61)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1962-86, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3262-65)
  - Music
    See: Series VIII, Music, Box 142, folder 3338
  - Nature, 1972-84, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3266-67)
  - Politics and economics, 1946-86, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3268-73)
  - Pound, Ezra
    - Biographical profiles and memoirs, 1958-85, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3274-75)
      See also: Oversize, box 158, folder 3713
    - Book reviews
      See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3714
      - Works about Pound, 1961-88, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3276-82)
      - Works by Pound, 1938-88, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 3283-84)
    - Brief mentions, 1950-88, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3285-88)
    - Conferences and exhibitions, 1972-88, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3289-92)
    - Editorials and letters to the Editor, 1930-88, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3293-95)
    - Essays and analysis, 1949-88, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3296-3300)
    - Interviews, 1958-65, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 3301)
    - Music by Pound: articles and reviews, 1923-88, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3302-04)
    - News articles, 1927-72, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3305-08)
    - News photographs, 1945-70, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3309)
      See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3715
    - Obituaries, 1972 Nov-Dec (Box 140, Folder 3310-11)
    - Scrapbooks kept by Olga Rudge, 1948-49, 1965 (Box 140, Folder 3312-14)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1967-84, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3315-16)
  - Psychiatry
    - General articles, 1962-82, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3317)
    - Szasz, Thomas S., 1972-80, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3318)
  - Rachewiltz, Mary and Boris de, 1949-87, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3319-20)
  - Religion, 1949-84, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3321-23)
  - Rudge, Olga, 1923-88, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3324-25)
    See also: Series VIII, Music, Box 142, folder 3338
  - Science and Technology
    - Fuller, R. Buckminster, 1964-84, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3326)
    - General articles, 1962-86, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3327)
  - Theater, 1965-86, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3328)
    See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3716
  - Venice, 1965-86, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3329-32)
  - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 3333-37)
- Music, 1911-89; Series VIII; 3; (6 boxes)
  Series VIII, Music, is housed in Boxes 142-47. The material is arranged alphabetically by subject and then by type of material.
  - ACCADEMIA MUSICALE CHIGIANA
    - Articles about, 1939-75, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3338)
    - Bullettino dell'Accademia musicale Chigiana, 1947-61 (Box 142, Folder 3339-46)
    - Calendars of events, 1957-78 (Box 142, Folder 3347)
    - Invitations, 1941-82, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3348)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1946-71, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3349-51)
    - Notes, 1952-64, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 3352-53)
    - Poster
      See: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3717
    - Programs, 1933-69, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3354-59)
    - Publications
      - Cherubini, Luigi. Pigmalione, rev. by Vito Frazzi. (libretto only) Siena, 1954 (Box 143, Folder 3360)
      - Galuppi, Baldassare. Passa Tempo al Cembalo: Suonate. Facsimile of manuscript. Siena, 1948 (Box 143, Folder 3361)
      - Vivaldi, Antonio. Juditha Triumphans, rev. and ed. Vito Frazzi and S. A. Luciani. (libretto only) Siena, 1941 (Box 143, Folder 3362)
    - Publicity, 1934-65, n.d (Box 143, Folder 3363)
  - ANTHEIL, GEORGE
    - Announcements, 1926, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3364)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1925-30, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3365)
    - Programs, 1930 (Box 143, Folder 3366)
  - CONCERTI TIGULLIANI
    - Announcement boards, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3367)
    - Announcement sheets, [1933-38] (Box 143, Folder 3368)
    - Flyers by Ezra Pound, 1933, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3369)
    - "Inverno musicale nel Tigullio", 1955-75 (Box 143, Folder 3370)
    - Newspaper clippings
      - Il Mare (includes articles by Ezra Pound, Basil Bunting and the Rev. Desmond Chute), 1933-39, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3371-73)
      - Miscellaneous, 1933-39, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3374-75)
    - Programs and publicity, 1933-39, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3376)
    - Scrapbook, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 3377)
    - Scrapbook pages, 1938, 1949 (Box 143, Folder 3378)
    - Ticket, 1934 (Box 143, Folder 3379)
  - POUND, EZRA
    - Le Testament
      - Notes by Olga Rudge, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3380)
      - Printed material, 1971-85, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 3381)
        See also: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3718
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Calendars of seasons and conferences, 1929-85, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3382-86)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1923-88, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 3387-96)
    - Periodicals
      - Recorder News, 1964-67 (Box 145, Folder 3397)
      - La Revue Musicale, 1926 Nov 1 (Box 145, Folder 3398)
      - La Silurante musicale, 1961 Nov (Box 145, Folder 3399)
    - Programs, 1911-89 (Box 145, Folder 3400-10)
    - Publicity for musicians, 1930-78, n.d. (Box 145, Folder 3411-12)
  - RUDGE, OLGA
    - Announcements and programs, 1913-37 (Box 145, Folder 3413-20)
    - Notices and reviews, 1916-31, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3421-24)
    - Publicity, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3425)
    - Scrapbook, 1911-19 (Box 146, Folder 3426-32)
  - SCORES
    - Manuscript
      - Antheil, George
        - Sonata for Solo Violin. Holograph manuscript, signed, annotated by Olga Rudge, [1923?]
          See: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3719
        - Sonata for Violin and Fortepiano: for Olga Rudge. Holograph manuscript, signed, annotated, 1923
          See: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3720
        - Sonata for Violin and Pianoforte. Holograph manuscript, signed, incomplete, 1923
          See: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3721
        - Troisieme Sonate pour violon et piano: For Mrs. Christian Gross, respectful hommage. Holograph manuscript, signed, annotated, n.d.
          See: Oversize, Box 158, folder 3722
      - Vivaldi, Antonio, 3722
        - Concerto in La: Manuscript in the hand of Ezra Pound, with incomplete pages in another hand
          See: Oversize, Box 159, folder 3723
        - Concerto Opus 6, No. 1 in Sol minore per violino solo e Orchestra. Transcribed and arranged by Gerhart Münch.
          See: Oversize, Box 159, folder 3724
        - Sette Sonate per violino e pianoforte, dalle XII Sonate per violino e basso (Op. 2): a cura dell'Instituto di Alta Cultura con la collaborazione dell'Accademia Chigiana Musicale. Arrangements, signed by Julia Perry, of Sonate IV, V, VI, XI, X, XI, and XII. Dedicated and inscribed to Olga Rudge, 1958-59
          See: Oversize, Box 159, folder 3725
        - Vivaldi, Antonio. Unidentified and incomplete scores in the hand of Ezra Pound, 1938-39, n.d.
          See: Oversize, Box 159, folders 3726-29
        - Vivaldi, Antonio. Miscellaneous and unidentified pages from transcriptions, many marked "Dresde," in the hand of Olga Rudge
          See: Oversize, Box 160, folder 3730
        - Unidentified, n.d.
          See: Oversize, Box 160, folder 3731
        - Miscellaneous manuscripts in the hand of Olga Rudge
          See: Oversize, Box 160, folder 3732 Miscellaneous manuscripts in the hand of others
          See: Oversize, Box 160, folder 3733
    - Printed
      - Bartok, Béla. Vierundvierzig Duos für zwei Violinen. Vienna: Universal-Edition A. G., c1933 (Box 146, Folder 3433)
      - Gagic, Bogdan. Partita za Klavir 1960. Zagreb, c1962 (Box 146, Folder 3434)
      - Heider, Werner. Commission für Stimme (Bariton) und Kammerenemble gedicht von Ezra Pound (1916). Studienpartitur. Frankfurt: Edition Peters No.8208
        See: Oversize, Box 160, folder 3734
      - Johannson, Bergt. Three Chansons- Kolme laulua ("The Tree"; "De Aegypto"; "Ité". Texts from Personae ). Helsinki: Edition Fazer, c1975 (Box 146, Folder 3435)
      - Károly, Hájos. "Mondja Édes kis Baba." Budapest: Rózsavölgyi & Co.", c1927
      - Unidentified page, n.d.
      - Pizzetti, Ildebrando. Sonata in la per pianoforte e violino: a Ernesto Consolo e a Mario Corti. Printed by J. & W. Chester, Ltd., c1920
      - Ravel, Maurice. A Hélène Jourdan- Morhange. Sonate pour Violon et Piano. Paris: Durand & Co., c1927
      - Reifling, Reimar. Piano Pedalling. Trans. from the Norwegian by Kathleen Dale. London: Oxford University Press, c1962 (Box 146, Folder 3436)
      - Vivaldi, Antonio
        - Concerto for Solo Violin or Oboe, Strings and Violin. Op. 8, No. 9. Edited by Sidney Beck. The New York Public Library, 1938
        - Gloria for Solo Voices, Mixed Chorus and Orchestra. Edited by Mason Martens. New York: Walton Music Corporation, c1961 (Box 146, Folder 3437)
      - Unsre Lieblinge die Schönsten Melodien für das Pianoforte zu vier Händen, mit einem Vorworte von Carl Reinecke. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel (Box 146, Folder 3438)
  - VIVALDI
    - Articles, 1937-74, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3439-40)
    - Congresso Internazionale del Biblioteche Musicale
      - Notes, typescript and typescript carbon, 1951, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3441)
      - Printed material, 1951 (Box 146, Folder 3442)
    - Guggenheim application materials, 1935-37 (Box 146, Folder 3443)
    - List of unedited vocal works at Turin, [1938?] (Box 146, Folder 3444)
    - Microfilm
      - Comments and notes by Ezra Pound and Olga Rudge (Box 146, Folder 3445)
      - "La Giro": typescript (probably by Pound), annotated by Ezra Pound and Olga Rudge (Box 146, Folder 3446)
      - "La Possibilita della microphotographia": typescript (intialled "O. R." but probably by Ezra Pound), corrected by Ezra Pound (Box 146, Folder 3447)
      - "Microphotographic Front:" typescript carbon, signed, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 3448)
      - Notes by Olga Rudge and Ezra Pound on envelopes that once contained photographs of Vivaldi scores (Box 147, Folder 3449-52)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1933-37, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3453)
    - Notebook, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3454)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3455-57)
    - Printed material, 1936-78, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3458-59)
    - Programs, 1939-78, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3460)
    - Research notebooks, 1927-30, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3461-62)
    - Research notes, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3463-64)
    - Text of the Dedication to Opus 9, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3465)
    - "Vivaldiana": photocopies, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 3466)
- Photographs, 1904-89; Series IX; 3.5; (7 boxes)
  Series IX, Photographs, is housed in Boxes 148-54 and is divided into six sections: Albums, Ezra Pound, Olga Rudge, Other Persons, Places, and Miscellaneous.
  - ALBUMS